- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- All right, guys. I'm just gonna say it.
好吧，伙计们。我就直说了。
I am loving Boulder Academy.
我非常喜欢博尔德学院。
- And I'm just gonna say it.
我也要直说。
I am loving our Uman Behavior class.
我非常喜欢我们的人类行为课。
- And I'm just gonna say it.
我也要直说。
It's human. Human, with an H.
是human，带H的。
- Oh, yeah? Then why does my book say Uman?
哦，是吗？那为什么我的书上写的是Uman？
- Because your thumb is over the H.
因为你的拇指盖住了H。
- Oh.
哦。
I guess that explains my Ath,
我想这解释了我的Ath，
Eography, and Panish classes.
Eography，和Panish课程。
- So, where are we gonna find a human
- 那么，我们要去哪里找一个人
to study for our human behavior project?
来研究我们的人类行为项目呢？
We're supposed to observe someone with issues
我们应该观察一个有困扰的人
and help them overcome them.
并帮助他们克服这些问题。
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
Here. I'll catch up with you guys later.
这里。我稍后会赶上你们。
all: ♪ A-E-I-O-U... ♪
♪ A-E-I-O-U... ♪
- Hey, guys, check out Dawn.
- 嘿，伙计们，看看Dawn。
- This is the third day in a row
she's stared into that room.
- What's going on with her?
- This is the third day in a row
you've stared into that room.
What's going on with you?
- Nothing. - Come on.
The tilted head... - The sappy smile...
- The breathy sigh.
- I know exactly what this is.
- This is textbook.
这是典型的。
- You want to be in glee club.
你想加入欢乐合唱团。
- She's crushing on a boy.
她对某个男孩有好感。
- [sighs] I totally do.
我完全有。
- She totally is.
她确实有。
- You've got a thing to sing.
你有唱歌的冲动。
- She's in the mood for dude.
她对某个男生有感觉。
- Well, they're holding auditions this week.
嗯，他们这周正在举行试镜。
You should try out.
你应该去试试。
- Oh, I couldn't.
哦，我不行。
Could I?
我可以吗？
No, I shouldn't.
不，我不应该。
Should I?
我应该吗？
But I can't.
但我不能。
But can I?
但我可以吗？
- Okay, I'm just gonna jump in here.
好吧，我这就插句话。
Why can't you?
为什么你不能？
- Well, I mean, I've sung for you,
嗯，我是说，我为你唱过歌，
and in the shower,
在淋浴时，
and in Oz in my dreams,
还有在我梦中的奥兹国，
but the one time I tried to sing in front of people
但有一次我试着在大家面前唱歌
was at an audition when I was seven.
是在我七岁时的试镜
And it didn't go so good.
结果不太好
- I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
- 我肯定没那么糟
- I yodeled, Mae.
- 我唱了约德尔调，梅
- Yodeled? Why would you yodel?
- 约德尔调？你为什么要唱那个？
- I don't know.
- 我不知道
Maybe 'cause I was nerv-- ♪ Who-who! ♪
也许是因为我紧张——♪哇-哇！♪
Yep, I'm a nervous yodeler.
没错，我是个紧张的约德尔歌手
- Oh, yeah. She's got an eye for that guy.
- 哦，是的。她对那家伙有意思
- She's got it bad for that lad.
她对那小伙子情有独钟。
- Ooh, I've got one.
哦，我有一个主意。
Looks like we found the subject
看来我们找到了研究对象
for our human behavior project.
来完成我们的人类行为项目。
- And you ruined it. - Wait, I've got more.
你毁了这一切。
- Just get away from us.
等等，我还有更多。
[upbeat music]
离我们远点。
- ♪ ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
欢快的音乐
[laughter]
笑声
- I wonder what they're talking about.
我想知道他们在谈论什么。
- Dawn, if you really wanna be in Glee Club that bad,
Dawn，如果你真的那么想加入Glee Club，
just audition.
就去试镜吧。
What do you have to lose?
你有什么可失去的？
- My dignity. My pride. My name.
我的尊严。我的骄傲。我的名字。
- Your name? - Yeah. I mean, just ask him.
你的名字？ - 是的。我是说，去问他。
He sneezed in his audition last year,
他在去年的试镜中打了个喷嚏，
and now he's "Snot Rocket Scott."
现在大家都叫他“鼻涕火箭”斯科特。
- Could've been Snotty Scotty.
本来也可能是“鼻涕斯科蒂”。
- His name is Mike!
他叫迈克！
- Hmm. Human Behavior Project journal entry one.
嗯。人类行为学项目日记第一条。
We are observing subject to help her get over her desire
我们正在观察对象，以帮助她克服对那位无法得到的骑士的渴望。
for that unattainable squire.
有什么结论吗？
Any conclusions?
有。那个也不行。
- Yes.
That one wasn't good either.
- What are you boys up to?
- 你们在搞什么鬼？
- Just working on our project for Human Behavior class.
- 我们正在为人类行为课做项目。
- We have to help someone with deep behavioral issues.
- 我们需要帮助一个有严重行为问题的人。
- Ooh, your father's available.
- 哦，你爸爸有空。
- Oh, Anne, please.
- 哦，安妮，拜托。
I do not have issues.
我没有问题。
- He has been sleep-eating again.
- 他又开始梦游吃东西了。
He sleepwalks right to the fridge and chows down.
他梦游直接走到冰箱前大吃特吃。
- Wha-where are you getting this?
- 你从哪儿听来的？
- Ah, right there.
- 啊，就在那儿。
It looks like you're hiding a chicken under your shirt.
看起来你好像在衬衫下藏了一只鸡。
- I have to poke it. - I gotta poke.
我得戳一下。
- [giggles] Everybody stop poking!
大家都别戳了！
Fine, I have a problem.
好吧，我承认我有问题。
So, can you, uh,
那么，你能，呃，
can you help Tommy's tummy?
你能帮Tommy的肚子吗？
- The problem seems a little too...
这个问题似乎有点...
fat.
太胖了。
- Hon!
亲爱的！
- What? They got to.
怎么了？他们必须得。
- Dawn, I've heard you sing.
Dawn, 我听过你唱歌。
And you're really good.
而且你真的很棒。
You should go for it.
你应该去试试。
- You're just saying that just 'cause you're my best friend.
你这么说只是因为你是我的好朋友。
- Fine. You want brutal honesty?
好吧。你想要残酷的诚实吗？
Let's ask your brothers.
让我们问问你的兄弟们。
- Human Behavior Project journal entry two:
人类行为项目日志条目二：
we've been invited into the belly of the beast,
我们被邀请进入怪物的腹地，
so we're leaving...
所以我们正离开...
the belly of the beast.
怪物的腹地。
- Dawn needs your opinion on something,
- 道恩需要你对某件事发表意见，
and we need you to be brutally honest.
- 我们需要你绝对诚实。
- She doesn't have a chance. - Give up now.
- 她没机会的。 - 现在就放弃吧。
- That guy is way out of her league.
- 那家伙完全超出她的水平。
- Dawn's not talking about a guy.
- 道恩说的不是个男的。
She wants to join the Glee Club.
她想加入欢乐合唱团。
[together] Ohhh.
[一起] 哦。
- Project's off. - Back to Tubby Tommy.
- 项目取消了。 - 回到胖汤米。
- But she won't audition
- 但她不会去试镜
because she's terrified to sing in public.
因为她害怕在公共场合唱歌。
It's a real issue.
这确实是个问题。
[together] Aww.
[一起] 哎呀。
- Project's back on. - Chicken Gut's on his own.
- 计划又启动了。 - 鸡肠子自己搞定。
- Dawn, I'm not sure if you're aware,
- 唐恩，我不确定你是否知道，
but we're taking a Human Behavior class.
但我们正在上人类行为课。
I think we can help you.
我觉得我们可以帮你。
- You help me?
- 你帮我？
Why, what's in it for you?
为什么，这对你们有什么好处？
- [scoffs] Dawn.
- [嗤笑] 唐恩。
Dawny Bear. Dawndelion.
唐恩熊。唐恩蒲公英。
Why does there have to be anything in it for us?
为什么我们非得从中得到什么好处呢？
- Because there's always something in it for you.
因为你们总是有所图。
Besides, what could you have possibly learned in that class
再说了，你在那课上学到了什么
that's gonna help me?
能帮到我？
- Come on, Dawn, if you know our techniques in advance,
拜托，Dawn，如果你事先知道我们的技巧，
you might not be receptive.
你可能就不会那么容易接受了。
Eh? Eh?
嗯？嗯？
[together] Eh? Eh?
- I can't believe I'm saying this,
我简直不敢相信我会这么说，
but...
但是...
I'm in.
我加入。
- Huh?
啊？
[rock music]
摇滚音乐
- So, Dawn, tell us about your childhood.
那么，Dawn，跟我们说说你的童年吧。
- It was the same as yours.
和你们的差不多。
- Hmm, interesting.
嗯，有意思。
- What about your relationship with your parents?
那你和父母的关系呢？
- Same as yours.
和你们的一样。
- Hmm, interesting.
嗯，有意思。
- Now, I'm going to say a word
现在，我要说一个词
and you say the first thing that pops into your mind.
我说一个词，你说出第一个浮现在脑海里的东西。
Taco. - Delicious.
墨西哥卷饼。- 美味。
- How is any of this helping?
- 这些怎么能帮到我？
I mean, you should be asking me questions like,
我的意思是，你应该问我这样的问题，
"What are you afraid of?
'你害怕什么？
What are your fears?"
你的恐惧是什么？'
- Oh, Dawn.
- 哦，道恩。
I think we know the questions to ask.
我想我们知道该问什么问题。
So what are you afraid of? What are your fears?
那么，你害怕什么？你的恐惧是什么？
- Well, I'm afraid I'm going to put myself out there
- 嗯，我害怕我会在全合唱团面前，
in front of the entire Glee Club,
在全Glee俱乐部面前，
get really nervous, open my mouth,
我会非常紧张，张开嘴，
and all that's gonna come out is a yodel.
结果只会发出约德尔调。
- A yodel?
约德尔调？
- Yeah. I mean, it's my secret shame.
是的。我是说，这是我秘密的羞愧。
When I was seven, I had a singing audition
当我七岁的时候，我有一次唱歌试镜，
and I got so nervous,
我太紧张了，
I opened my mouth and yodeled.
我张开嘴，结果唱出了约德尔调。
For no reason.
没有任何原因。
- Well, in my experience, there's always a reason.
嗯，根据我的经验，总是有原因的。
Do you think she knows we're the reason?
你觉得她知道是我们搞的鬼吗？
- Maybe we can test her and find out.
也许我们可以试探她，看看她是否知道。
- So, do you have any recollection of where
那么，你还记得这种约德尔唱法是从哪里来的吗？
this yodeling came from?
不记得。
- No. - Hmm.
嗯。
Or who it may have come from?
或者它可能是从谁那里来的？
- None whatsoever.
完全没有头绪。
- So you don't remember the three of us
所以你不记得我们三个在你床边练习约德尔唱法，而你当时正在睡觉？
practicing our yodeling right next to your bed
不记得。
while you were sleeping?
我们做得不错，伙计们。
- No.
不记得。
- We're good, guys.
我们没事，伙计们。
- W-wait, what do you mean
等等，你是什么意思？
you yodeled while I slept?
你们在我睡觉时唱约德尔调？
- Pfff, yodeling.
噗，唱约德尔调。
- Us?
我们？
- Lie down.
躺下。
I'm going to say a word--
我要说一个词——
[together] We're so sorry, Dawn!
我们非常抱歉，Dawn！
- When we were seven, Mom took you to soccer,
我们七岁的时候，妈妈带你去踢足球，
but Dad took us to yodeling.
但爸爸带我们去学约德尔唱法。
He wanted us to compete!
他想让我们比赛！
- It was our secret shame!
- 那是我们的秘密耻辱！
So we practiced at night when no one could hear us.
所以我们晚上练习，没人能听到我们。
- It must have gotten into your head while you were sleeping
- 这肯定在你睡觉时进入了你的脑海
and that's why you yodeled.
这就是为什么你会约德尔唱。
- Can I just have a taco now?
- 我现在可以吃个塔可吗？
- [scoffs] Seriously?
- [嗤之以鼻] 真的吗？
Late-night yodeling?
深夜约德尔唱？
You're just making that up to give me a reason why I yodeled.
你只是在编造这个理由来解释我为什么会约德尔唱。
- Does this sound like we're making it up?
- 这听起来像是我们编造的吗？
Eins, zwei. Eins, zwei, drei, bier.
一，二。一，二，三，啤酒。
[yodeling]
[唱山歌]
- Wow.
- 哇。
And wow.
哇。
So it was yodel-ehe-you.
所以是山歌-哎-哟。
You and your late night yodeling did get into my head.
你和你的深夜山歌确实进入了我的脑海。
- But now that you know it's us
- 但现在你知道是我们
that caused it, you should be cured?
引起的，你应该痊愈了吧？
Eh? Eh?
嗯？嗯？
[together] Eh? Eh?
- Huh.
嗯。
You're right.
你说得对。
I mean, it wasn't my fault.
我的意思是，这不是我的错。
It was your fault.
是你的错。
I can't believe I'm saying this,
真不敢相信我这么说，
but... maybe I am cured.
但是...也许我真的好了。
Thanks, guys.
谢谢，伙计们。
- You're welcome.
不客气。
Subject is cured.
患者已治愈。
Therapists feel humiliated.
治疗师们感到羞辱。
♪ ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
- ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- So your brothers' therapy session
- 所以你哥哥们的治疗会话
really worked?
真的有效？
- I think it did. I mean. I'm not nervous at all.
- 我想是的。我的意思是，我一点也不紧张。
Ooh, signup.
哦，报名。
- Big day, huh?
- 大日子，是吧？
- Yup.
- 是的。
- Hi. I'm Brooklyn,
嗨，我是布鲁克林，
Glee Club Captain.
欢乐合唱团的队长。
- Hi. I'm Dawn.
嗨，我是Dawn。
- I'm Moo.
我是Moo。
I moon Mae.
我叫Mae。
I mean Moe.
我是说Moe。
Why am I nervous?
我为什么紧张？
- I don't know, but I'm not.
我不知道，但我并不紧张。
- It's okay. Everybody gets nervous.
没关系，每个人都会紧张的。
- Mae!
Mae！
My name's Mae. I'm not auditioning.
我叫Mae，我不是来试镜的。
- I am.
我是。
- You know what helps nervous hopefuls?
你知道什么能帮助紧张的希望者吗？
- Not nervous.
不紧张。
- The Welcome Song. It calms the nerves.
《欢迎歌》。它能安抚紧张的情绪。
- My nerves are fine.
我的情绪很好。
- ♪ Wellllcome ♪
♪ 欢 迎 ♪
♪ To the nerrrvous ♪
♪ 给 紧 张 的 ♪
♪ Giiirrrl ♪
♪ 女 孩 ♪
What's your name again? - Dawn.
你叫什么名字来着？ - Dawn。
Not nervous.
不紧张。
- ♪ Dawwwwnn ♪
♪ 道恩 ♪
♪ "Not Nervous" Dawwwwnn ♪
♪ '不紧张' 道恩 ♪
- It's just Dawn.
就是道恩。
- ♪ Welcome to the not nervous ♪
♪ 欢迎来到不紧张 ♪
♪ Juuusst ♪
♪ 就 ♪
♪ Dawwwnnn ♪
♪ 道恩 ♪
[applause]
[掌声]
I hope that helped.
希望这有帮助。
- It did.
确实有帮助。
I feel much better.
我感觉好多了。
- I don't!
我可不这么觉得！
Now I'm nervous.
现在我紧张了。
She's so good.
她太厉害了。
- First up,
首先上场的是，
Dawn Harper.
Dawn Harper。
- [stammering] Maybe I don't belong here.
也许我不属于这里。
- Yes, you do.
不，你属于这里。
You got this, Dawn.
你能行的，Dawn。
- Mae's right. You got this.
Mae说得对，你能行的。
Just don't think about yodeling.
只是不要想约德尔唱法。
[yodeling]
（约德尔唱法）
- Okay.
好的。
You're good now.
你现在很好。
- Ms. Harper, whenever you're ready.
哈珀女士，你准备好了就请开始。
- Eeeeeee.
咿咿咿咿咿。
[clears throat]
（清嗓子）
Eeeeeee.
咿咿咿咿咿。
Run!
跑！
- At least she didn't yodel.
至少她没有唱约德尔调。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- I can't believe this.
我简直不敢相信。
I'm so humiliated.
我感到如此羞辱。
- Come on, Dawn. It wasn't that bad.
来吧，Dawn，没那么糟糕。
- Really? It's all over FaceShack.
真的吗？这已经在FaceShack上到处都是了。
The AV Club even made a mashup of me talking to a dolphin.
AV俱乐部甚至做了一个我和海豚对话的混搭视频。
Eeeee. [chittering]
Eeeee。[吱吱声]
- [laughing] Wait.
[笑]等等。
What were you and the dolphin talking about?
你和海豚在聊什么？
- Oh, not much. I mean, he was just telling me
哦，没什么。我是说，他只是在告诉我
that my dream of being in Glee Club is officially over.
我加入欢乐合唱团的梦想正式结束了。
- You got all that from an "eeee?"
你就从那个“eeee”中听出了这么多？
Fascinating language.
真是一种迷人的语言。
- Don't worry, Dawn. We can fix this.
别担心，Dawn。我们能解决这个。
- No. I'm done.
不。我放弃了。
I'm done auditioning, I'm done singing,
我不再试镜，不再唱歌，
and I'm definitely done with you guys getting in my head.
也绝对不再让你们这些家伙影响我的想法。
Huh? Huh? Uh-uh.
嗯？嗯？呃-呃。
- This is terrible. - I know.
- 这太糟糕了。 - 我知道。
We'll never get an A in Human Behavior now.
我们永远也拿不到人类行为课的A了。
- No, not the grade. I feel bad about Dawn.
- 不，不是成绩。我对Dawn感到难过。
- Yeah, I feel bad about Dawn, too.
- 是啊，我也为Dawn感到难过。
- We all feel bad about Dawn.
- 我们都为Dawn感到难过。
But for once, why don't we put ourselves first?
但这一次，我们为什么不先考虑自己呢？
- We always put ourselves first.
- 我们总是先考虑自己。
- Then what are we arguing about?
- 那我们还在争论什么呢？
- But Dawn just said she's tired of us getting in her head.
- 但Dawn刚刚说她厌倦了我们影响她的思绪。
- What if she doesn't know we're there?
- 如果她不知道我们在那里呢？
Human Behavior Project entry 26:
人类行为项目条目26：
we know from past yodeling incident
我们从过去的约德尔事件中知道
that subject is susceptible to suggestion when she sleeps.
当她睡觉时，受试者容易受到暗示。
- Are you sure this hypnosis stuff we got off the internet
- 你确定我们从网上弄来的这些催眠东西
is gonna work?
- 会有效吗？
- Trust me, it'll work,
- 相信我，会有效的，
especially on a heavy sleeper.
- 特别是对一个沉睡者。
When you hear two claps, you will be transformed.
当你听到两声拍手，你将会被转变。
You will become a strong-willed, confident teenage girl.
你将成为一个意志坚强、自信的少女。
You will be so confident
你将会如此自信
that you will want to redo your audition
以至于你想要重新参加试镜
with no fear of failure.
不再害怕失败。
Okay, I think that should do it.
好的，我想这样应该可以了。
- That's it?
就这样？
That's not enough to restore her confidence.
这不足以恢复她的信心。
- Yeah. Give her some swag.
是啊。给她一些酷劲。
- That was a perfectly appropriate amount of swag.
那已经是非常合适的酷劲了。
- The fact that you just said it like that
你刚刚那样说
proves you know nothing about swag.
证明你对酷劲一无所知。
- Subject is stirring! Let's .go
目标开始动了！我们走吧
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
啦啦啦啦啦啦
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
啦啦啦啦啦
- She's coming.
她来了。
- Ah! - Oh!
啊！- 哦！
- That was more of a "she's here."
那更像是‘她已经到了’。
- What? - Nothing.
什么？- 没事。
- How'd you sleep?
你睡得怎么样？
- Well...
嗯...
I dreamt I auditioned for a dolphin glee club,
我梦见我去海豚合唱团试音，
and even they didn't want me.
就连它们都不想要我。
Or should I say,
或者我应该说，
meeeeee.
我。。。。。。
I'm never auditioning for anything ever again.
我再也不参加任何试镜了。
- We'll see about that.
我们走着瞧。
[claps]
Feeling any more confident?
感觉更有信心了吗？
- More confident?
更有信心？
Ha! I laughed.
哈！我笑了。
Ha! I laughed again.
哈！我又笑了。
I don't lack confidence.
我并不缺乏自信。
The only thing I lack is my breakfast sushi.
我唯一缺少的就是我的早餐寿司。
So where's my tuna tataki?
那我的金枪鱼塔塔基呢？
- What's she tatalking about?
- 她在说什么呢？
- This is just a guess,
- 这只是个猜测，
but...
但是...
I don't think Ricky gave you enough confidence.
我觉得Ricky给你的信心还不够。
You're not just a good singer; you're a star.
你不只是一个好歌手；你是明星。
No. A megastar!
不。是超级巨星！
Like those divas who eat sushi for every meal.
就像那些每餐都吃寿司的歌后。
- I told you I had it covered.
- 我告诉过你我搞定了。
- Um, hello?
嗯，有人吗？
[snaps] BeyDawncé doesn't like to wait.
BeyDawncé不喜欢等人。
- BeyDawncé? Where is that coming from?
BeyDawncé？这名字哪来的？
- You're the greatest singer in the world.
你是世界上最伟大的歌手。
You own every stage you step on.
你踏上每一个舞台都主宰全场。
You're not Dawn; you're...
你不是Dawn；你是...
[snaps] BeyDawncé!
BeyDawncé！
- Oh, please. No pictures, no pictures.
哦，拜托。不要拍照，不要拍照。
- Nobody's taking your picture.
没人要给你拍照。
- Oh, no, I just don't want these pictures on the fridge.
哦，不，我只是不想把这些照片放在冰箱上。
More me, less you.
多展现我，少展现你。
- Okay, you have got to snap her out of this!
- 好吧，你得让她清醒过来！
- Right! Snap her out of it.
- 对！让她清醒过来。
How do I snap her out of it?
我怎么让她清醒过来？
- You don't know?!
- 你不知道？！
- I read about how to hypnotize her,
- 我读过如何催眠她，
not how to dehypnotize her.
但没读过如何解除催眠。
- Come on, pants. You got this!
- 来吧，裤子。你能做到的！
[inhales]
[吸气]
- You talking to your pants again?
- 你又在跟你的裤子说话了？
Tom, do you even hear me?
汤姆，你有在听我说吗？
- [gasps]
（倒吸气）
Why did my mom buy me these pants?
为什么我妈要给我买这条裤子？
They're, like, totes made for boys.
它们明明就是男生穿的。
But I can still pull them off because I'm a strong-willed,
不过凭我坚强的意志和自信的少女魅力，我还是能驾驭，但我并不想这么做。
confident teenage girl, but I don't wanna.
汤姆，你还好吗？
- Tom, are you okay?
别对我指手画脚！
- Stop judging me!
为什么你们要害我？!
Why are you trying to ruin my life?!
汤姆？我觉得我们应该让男生们检查一下你！
- Tom? I really think we should have the boys examine you!
滚出我的房间！
- Get out of my room!
- 滚出我的房间！
- Well, I'm off to Glee Club.
- 好吧，我要去合唱团了。
- Wait! You can't go to school and audition for the Glee Club.
- 等等！你不能去学校并且试镜合唱团。
- Oh, whoever said I was gonna audition?
- 哦，谁说我打算试镜了？
I'm gonna march down there so they can beg me
我要大摇大摆地走过去，让他们求我
to join their little group.
加入他们的小团体。
- Maybe making them beg isn't the best approach.
- 也许让他们求你不是最好的方法。
- Oh, well, certainly not dressed like this.
- 哦，当然，肯定不能穿成这样。
Scoot scoot.
快走快走。
I look so basic.
我看起来太普通了。
And there's nothing basic about
而且BeyDawncé一点也不普通
[snaps] BeyDawncé.
[响指] BeyDawncé
- Search for the answer faster!
- 快点找到答案！
It's not my fault Dad would only pay for the slow wi-fi.
这不是我的错，老爸只肯付慢速网络的钱
- This is bad. BeyDawncé is going to ruin Dawn's chances
- 这很糟糕，BeyDawncé会毁了Dawn进入合唱团的机会
of ever getting into that Glee Club.
- 她不见了！
- She's gone!
- 来吧，我在路上查怎么修复她
- Come on. I'll research how to fix her on the way.
[摇滚音乐]
[rock music]
- 拜拜！
- Ta-ta!
[喘气]你好~。Miles，你看起来想要个签名呢。
[gasps] Hellooo.
[倒抽一口气] 你好啊。
Miles, you look like you want an autograph.
Miles，你看起来像是要签名。
Here.
给你。
- Hey, that's my math homework.
- 嘿，那是我的数学作业。
- Well, now it's a collector's item.
- 嗯，现在它是收藏品了。
You're welcome.
不用谢。
- What is happening?
- 发生了什么？
- I don't know,
- 我不知道，
but I bet the boys did something stupid.
但我敢打赌是那些男孩做了什么蠢事。
- We did something stupid!
- 我们做了什么蠢事！
- See, we may have tried to hypnotize Dawn
- 看，我们可能试图催眠Dawn
to give her enough confidence
让她有足够的信心
to audition for the Glee Club again.
再次参加Glee Club的试镜。
- And we may have gone too far and turned her into a diva.
- 而我们可能做得太过火，把她变成了一个歌剧女主角。
- And I may have definitely named her BeyDawncé.
- 而我可能确实给她起了个名字叫BeyDawncé。
- Until I can figure out how to get her back to being just Dawn,
- 在我找到如何让她变回原来的Dawn之前，
we need to keep her from going into the Glee Club.
我们需要阻止她进入Glee Club。
- Too late. BeyDawncé's begonecé.
- 太晚了。BeyDawncé已经走了。
- Sorry I'm late, people.
- 对不起，我迟到了，各位。
- You came back!
- 你回来了！
♪ Wellllcome back ♪
♪ 欢迎回来 ♪
♪ To the braaave giiirrrl ♪
♪ 给勇敢的女孩 ♪
- That's adorable.
真可爱。
But you're a little pitchy, sweetheart.
但你的音调有点偏，亲爱的。
I would have done it more like this.
我会做得更像这样。
[clears throat]
（清嗓子）
♪ Thank you for welcoming meeeee ♪
♪ 谢谢你们的欢迎 ♪
♪ Agaaaain ♪
♪ 再次 ♪
What's your name again?
你叫什么名字来着？
- We met.
我们见过。
I'm Brooklyn.
我是布鲁克林。
- ♪ We meeettt ♪
♪我们见面了♪
♪ I'm Brooklynnnn! ♪
♪我是布鲁克林！♪
- Wow, she's good!
哇，她真厉害！
- My nervous song always helps.
我的紧张歌曲总是有帮助。
- Dawn's going up on stage.
Dawn要上台了。
- I'll stall her.
我会拖延她。
You need to dehypnotize her now.
你现在需要让她解除催眠。
- BeyDawncé, listen.
BeyDawncé，听着。
A star like you s--
像你这样的明星——
a megastar like you shouldn't waste your talent
像你这样的巨星不应该浪费你的才华
on this silly little Glee Club.
在这个小小的Glee俱乐部上。
- You're right.
- 你说得对。
The whole world needs to see this.
全世界都需要看到这个。
Film me.
拍我。
- It says here while she was being hypnotized,
- 这里说在她被催眠的时候，
I was supposed to suggest a trigger
我应该提出一个触发器
to snap her out of it.
让她从中清醒过来。
But I didn't do that.
但我没有这么做。
- Then the trigger could be anything.
- 那么触发器可以是任何东西。
- Ooh! Animal noises!
哦！动物的声音！
- I don't do animal noises.
我不模仿动物的声音。
- Just make noise!
随便发出点声音！
[cacophony]
（嘈杂声）
- Wow. Impressive.
哇。真厉害。
- I've got deep pits.
我有深邃的低音。
[cacophony]
（嘈杂声）
- Listen to my wild fans.
听听我狂热的粉丝们。
They're hungry for [snaps] BeyDawncé.
他们渴望[打响指]BeyDawncé。
- ♪ Wellll here's a little taste for yooou ♪
♪ 好吧，给你一点小小的尝鲜 ♪
♪ So open your earrrrrs and don't leave ♪
♪ Until you're satisfiiiied ♪
- Well, it's good to see you back, my dear,
but save yourself for the audition.
- Audition?
I think it's pretty clear that I do not need to audition.
- Dawn-- - Uh, uh, uh.
It's BeyDawncé.
And you're in my light.
So, scoot scoot.
[chuckles] ♪ Scoot, scoot, scoot ♪
咯咯笑
- I got it!
我明白了！
I said she'd transform when she heard two claps.
我说过她听到两声掌声就会变身。
But I never said in or out, so maybe it'll work both ways.
但我没说变好还是变坏，所以可能两种情况都存在。
- Um, where am I?
嗯，我在哪儿？
And--and why am I dressed like this?
还有，为什么我会穿成这样？
- We'll explain in the hall.
我们在走廊解释。
- They're hungry for BeyDawncé.
他们渴望着碧昂黛oncé。
♪ Well, here's a little taste for yoooou ♪ - Wow. I can't believe you guys used me
好吧，给你一点尝尝～
as some sort of guinea pig.
哇，真不敢相信你们把我当小白鼠。
♪ Until you're satisfiiiied ♪ - Whoa.
♪ 直到你心满意足 ♪
I sound really good.
哇，我听起来真不错。
And I'm sounding good in front of people.
而且在众人面前我也唱得很好。
I'm not yodeling or squeaking like a dolphin.
我没有像山羊那样叫，也没有像海豚那样尖叫。
I'm actually singing.
我真的在唱歌。
- So now that we've shown you you can sing in public,
现在我们已经证明了你可以在公共场合唱歌，
you're not mad at us?
所以你就不生我们的气了吗？
- Well of course I'm mad at you.
嗯，我当然还是生你们的气。
But you helped me realize
但是你们帮我意识到
that if BeyDawncé has that kind of confidence,
如果BeyDawncé有那种自信，
and I'm her, then I should have that confidence deep inside too.
如果我是BeyDawncé，那么我也应该拥有那种深藏不露的自信。
- What do you know?
- 你知道什么？
For once, things actually worked out and nothing bad happened.
这一次，事情居然真的顺利，没有发生任何坏事。
- Tom, Tom, Tom, Tom.
- 汤姆，汤姆，汤姆，汤姆。
You don't actually go to school here.
你其实不在这里上学。
We are just here because the kids forgot their lunches.
我们只是因为孩子们忘了带午餐才来这里的。
- I have to find Jenny. I have so much to tell her.
- 我得找到珍妮。我有很多话要告诉她。
- You don't think we...
- 你不觉得我们...
- I should probably dehypnotize him.
- 我可能应该解除对他的催眠。
- No, not yet.
- 不，还不是时候。
Let's see how this plays out.
让我们看看这会怎么发展。
- You hand me that phone right now...
- 你现在就把那手机给我...
young lady.
小姑娘。
- [gasps]
- [吸气声]
I hate you!
我恨你！
- 8-6-7-5-3-OMG.
- 8-6-7-5-3-哦，我的天。
He does know a Jenny.
他确实认识一个叫Jenny的人。
- Now, if you'll excuse me...
- 现在，如果你们不介意的话...
There's something I need to do
我有件事需要去做
♪ I'm much more than this world has planned for me ♪
♪ 我远不止这个世界为我计划的 ♪
♪ Bigger than the box they made to hold me ♪
♪ 超越他们为我设定的框架 ♪
♪ And all the roads may change ♪
♪ 所有道路都可能改变 ♪
♪ And life rearrange ♪
♪ 生活也会重新安排 ♪
♪ It is only... ♪ - Wow, she really is good.
♪ 这只是... ♪ - 哇，她真的很棒。
- I've inspired another one.
- 我又启发了一个。
- ♪ I'll be unstoppable, whoa ♪
- ♪ 我将势不可挡，哇 ♪
- That's my best friend up there.
- 那是我的好朋友。
- And that's our sister.
- 那是我们的姐姐。
- And that's our dad.
- 那是我们的爸爸。
- Your headband is totes adorbs.
- 你的发带真是超级可爱。
- ♪ Unstoppable, whoa ♪
♪ 我将势不可挡，哇 ♪
[applause]
[掌声]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪